<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:opensearch="http://a9.com/-/spec/opensearch/1.1/" xmlns:s="http://jadedpixel.com/-/spec/shopify">
  <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news.atom</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news.atom"/>
  <title>One Wholesale - Topics</title>
  <updated>2019-04-25T14:25:00-04:00</updated>
  <author>
    <name>One Wholesale</name>
  </author>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/marijuana-health-benefits-why-the-herb-is-healthy</id>
    <published>2019-04-25T14:25:00-04:00</published>
    <updated>2019-04-26T16:09:02-04:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/marijuana-health-benefits-why-the-herb-is-healthy"/>
    <title>Marijuana Health Benefits: Why the Herb is Healthy?</title>
    <author>
      <name>Ali Sadr</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span>Today, there are </span><span>millions of individuals the world over</span><span> who smoke marijuana for either recreational or medicinal purposes. Unlike back in the day, people now understand the benefits of marijuana and the same have been proven scientifically.</span></p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/marijuana-health-benefits-why-the-herb-is-healthy">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Today, there are </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">millions of individuals the world over</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> who smoke marijuana for either recreational or medicinal purposes. Unlike back in the day, people now understand the benefits of marijuana and the same have been proven scientifically. </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Health Benefits of Marijuana</span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">If you’re wondering what health benefits marijuana may offer, we’ve got a few! </span></p>
<h2><b>Pain Relief </b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The first and most obvious health benefit offered by marijuana is pain relief. People today take all sorts of stuff for pain relief and were not just talking about medical or chronic problems. People drop Advil for hangovers, IBuprofen for aches and pains and all sorts of other stuff to reduce unpleasant felt sensations. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The problem with all these is that though effective, they do a number on your liver functions. Marijuana in comparison is an effective form of pain mitigation without the liver strain caused by most other conventional allopathic pain medications. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In short, when it comes to pain relief with minimal side effects and strain on the body, marijuana is where it’s at! </span></p>
<h2><b>Harm Mitigation </b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">One thing that many who struggle with alcoholism and addiction to hard drugs is harm mitigation. It has been found that contrary to the gateway approach to marijuana, the herb is actually a great help when struggling with harmful addiction. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Many individuals who have previously been hooked onto substances like alcohol, amphetamines, heroin and even cocaine agree that balanced smoking helps reduce cravings. Unlike harder drugs, marijuana smoking does not create dozens of side effects. It does not trigger indecency, indiscretion or violence!</span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The herb also mitigates anxiety related to cravings when detoxing from such substances. In short, marijuana helps immensely with harm mitigation and cleaning up in general! </span></p>
<h2><b>Emotional Balance</b></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">Finally, smoking marijuana is a great way to unwind, pull back, relax and regulate emotionally. Marijuana has been an effective way to address various psycho-emotional complications including anxiety, depression and even issues with anger and rage. </span></p>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">In comparison to the many available SSRIs, anti-depressants and other medications offered for those suffering from emotional distress, smoking marijuana is possibly the most beneficial. Free of side effects and safe on the liver, marijuana beats most available psychotropic medication in most circumstances! </span></p>
<h2><span style="font-weight: 400;">Winding Down </span></h2>
<p><span style="font-weight: 400;">The benefits listed are just those that are proven and most commonly known. There are numerous other benefits to health that are associated with marijuana. In any case, being a </span><a href="https://www.bongoutlet.com/collections/bongs" title="bongoutlet quality bongs"><span style="font-weight: 400;">company that sells bongs</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">bubblers</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">dab rigs</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">oil rigs</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and all kinds of </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">smoking paraphernalia</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">accessories</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> to clients in </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">Canada</span><span style="font-weight: 400;"> and the </span><span style="font-weight: 400;">USonline</span><span style="font-weight: 400;">, we know what the culture is about!</span></p>
<a href="https://www.bongoutlet.com/pages/contact" title="bongoutlet contact customer service"><span style="font-weight: 400;">Connect with us</span></a><span style="font-weight: 400;"> if you’re looking for smoking accessories or more information! In any case, happy smoking! </span>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/how-to-clean-a-glass-bong</id>
    <published>2019-02-20T13:17:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-02-20T13:30:20-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/how-to-clean-a-glass-bong"/>
    <title>How To Clean A Glass Bong</title>
    <author>
      <name>James Park</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>According to estimates, 17% of the worldwide population will be avid smokers of tobacco by 2030. With the smoking culture in full swing, it’s rare to find people who are unaware of bongs or water pipes.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/how-to-clean-a-glass-bong">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>According to estimates, 17% of the worldwide population will be avid smokers of tobacco by 2030. With the smoking culture in full swing, it’s rare to find people who are unaware of bongs or water pipes.</p>
<p>A bong is a device used for filtering and cooling smoke. It’s commonly used in smoking cannabis, tobacco, CBD products, etc. Its design and structure allow it to remove the ash and carcinogens, and give smokers a comfortable experience with smoother rip.</p>
<p>As a bong user, you’ll need to clean your bong every once in a while, to keep it free from bacteria. Moreover, cleaning your bong will ensure you get a great smoking experience every time. To keep the smoking sessions one of their kind, here’s a comprehensive guide on cleaning your bong.</p>
<h1><b>Efficient Cleaning Solutions</b></h1>
<p>In order to clean the gunk stuck on the pipe’s insides, you’ll need an abrasive and efficient cleaning solution. You can use a variety of different pipe cleaners in the market or use a salt and isopropyl alcohol solution. If you’re making the alcohol and salt solution at home, take alcohol and salt in the ratio 2:1 to make an abrasive composition that’ll easily scrape the gunk off the glass. Moreover, you can keep the solution to soak a little before you scrape for easy cleaning. In case your pipe is composed of removable parts, separate the pieces and soak them in cleaning solution inside a plastic bag before you clean the pipe.</p>
<p>Be careful while cleaning your glass bong; it’ll get slippery. To avoid breakage, clean your bong over the sink and place a plastic tub or a mat over it. When the gunk becomes loose, rinse the pieces with water to remove the cleaning solution. Allow it to dry.</p>
<h1><b>Cleaning Of Percolators</b></h1>
<p>For those water pipes that include percolators, cleaning it with a solution can be quite tricky. To clean the percolator, simply fill the water pipe’s bottom with cleaning solution and shake it while covering the top with your palm. Drain the solution and rinse. Ensure that you rinse enough to get the solution out of the percolator otherwise it’ll affect the flavor.</p>
<h1><b>Cleaning Of Parts Made Out Of Other Materials </b></h1>
<p>If your bong is composed of titanium or ceramic pieces, you can heat them instead of using cleaning solutions. Upon heating the parts, the stuck gunk will liquefy which can be easily wiped away.</p>
<p>If you’re looking for cool bongs for sale in the US or Canada, reach out to us!</p>
<p>At <b>OneWholesale.ca</b> we offer an array of affordable bongs and other smoking accessories. Contact us for more details.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/marijuana-myths-5-ridiculous-myths-about-marijuana-busted</id>
    <published>2019-02-20T13:13:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-02-20T13:16:47-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/marijuana-myths-5-ridiculous-myths-about-marijuana-busted"/>
    <title>Marijuana Myths: 5 Ridiculous Myths about Marijuana Busted!</title>
    <author>
      <name>James Park</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>We know more about Marijuana today in the West scientifically speaking than we ever did before. Among the many things we know now; some include the fact that marijuana has medical benefits, it is safer than alcohol recreationally and that prohibition was a bad idea to begin with!</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/marijuana-myths-5-ridiculous-myths-about-marijuana-busted">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>We know more about Marijuana today in the West scientifically speaking than we ever did before. Among the many things we know now; some include the fact that marijuana has medical benefits, it is safer than alcohol recreationally and that prohibition was a bad idea to begin with!</p>
<p>At the same time, there are still individuals and elements that have trouble accepting that this herb is actually quite wonderful. The result; myths and misconceptions!</p>
<h1><b>Marijuana Myths and the Real Truth</b></h1>
<p>Out of the many myths surrounding marijuana today, we have put together some of the most common ones and proceeded to replace them with whatever the truth may be in the matter!</p>
<h2><b>Weed makes you Lose Sanity</b></h2>
<p>One of the oldest myths associated with marijuana and sadly, one that many still believe is that smoking marijuana makes you lose your mind in a sense. People have blamed the herb for everything from dementia to all out psychosis insisting that smoking or consuming marijuana was the sole cause.  </p>
<p>The truth is, marijuana does not under any circumstances drive people insane. There have been a few cases where people with pre-existing psychosis have been triggered by marijuana use. This being said, in the absence of an already present condition or the use of other drugs (anti-psychotics especially), marijuana does not cause any kind of psychosis to manifest.</p>
<h2><b>Weed Leads to Use of Other Drugs</b></h2>
<p>This one is a Regan administration favorite. The ‘Devils Lettuce’ pushing people to take on other substances. Not true! More than marijuana it was prohibition and the difficulty in knowing what your source is giving you that may have resulted in the use of other substances.</p>
<p>If someone is smoking marijuana, chances are that they are probably quite content with the same. The use and graduation to other drugs is a thing of personal choice. Don’t blame the herb!</p>
<h2><b>Marijuana Causes Cancer </b></h2>
<p>Many insist that smoking marijuana causes lung cancer and triggers other cancers as well! Though long term heavy smoking can cause respiratory complications if not balanced, cancer is by no means one of them. Quite the opposite – studies conducted have proven without a doubt that marijuana and what it contains actually inhibit the growth of malignant tumors!</p>
<h2><b>Marijuana Makes People Useless</b></h2>
<p>Not really! People choose to be useless! Marijuana may mellow you out depending on the strain you have smoked. That being said the effect does not last all day. Though there are many smokers who choose a sedentary lifestyle for themselves, this is usually put in place even before they start smoking. There are just as many high functioning successful and energetic individuals who smoke on a daily basis.  If you’re organized, clear with your schedules and good with you priorities, there is no reason why smoking marijuana should get in the way of that.</p>
<p>It’s kind of like saying a beer post work during dinner makes you an alcoholic. Utter nonsense!</p>
<h2><b>Marijuana Overdose Death is a Thing </b></h2>
<p>Okay, to be fair, there may be times when you have consumed an edible or tried out a new concentrate that knocks you off your feet to the point that you may think you’re unwell. The truth is, when it comes to marijuana and feeling like an over dose, it’s mostly in your head!</p>
<p>Tough having more THC and CBD in you then you can handle could rattle you depending on who you are, rest assured, if its marijuana you’re taking in, you’re not going to die! Have some water, give it a few hours, maybe grab a bite and get some sleep and this myth will disprove itself automatically!</p>
<h1><b>Winding Down </b></h1>
<p>There are a lot of other silly myths circulating against marijuana which hopefully you can spot. Remember, anything done in excess isn’t great be it food, exercise or yes, marijuana! That being said, if you smoke smart, schedule and keep doing the day to day things you need to, you needn’t worry about a thing (and no we’re not subtly quoting Bob Marley here)!</p>
<p>If you were reading this blog for kicks and giggles and simply wanted to pick up some new smoking equipment, check out online catalog, check out our cheap bongs, pipes and bubblers and have yourself a mellow day! </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/smoking-vs-drinking-5-things-that-make-mary-jane-safer</id>
    <published>2019-02-20T13:07:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-02-20T13:09:05-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/smoking-vs-drinking-5-things-that-make-mary-jane-safer"/>
    <title>Smoking Vs Drinking: 5 Things That Make Mary Jane Safer!</title>
    <author>
      <name>James Park</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>With the legalization of marijuana in Canada and in the U.S., there has been increased awareness about how the herb works and what it’s about. Propaganda spread during the time following good old Regan’s “War on Drugs” though laughable quickly spread and was believed by countless individuals on both sides of the border.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/smoking-vs-drinking-5-things-that-make-mary-jane-safer">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>With the legalization of marijuana in Canada and in the U.S., there has been increased awareness about how the herb works and what it’s about. Propaganda spread during the time following good old Regan’s “War on Drugs” though laughable quickly spread and was believed by countless individuals on both sides of the border.</p>
<p>What was funnier and still is the long standing consideration of alcohol to be the safer, more socially acceptable and legally permitted form of recreational substance use.</p>
<h1><b>What We Now Know</b></h1>
<p>Today however, things are very different. Gone are the days when a slurring alcoholic could point a finger at someone smoking cannabis as if the same was evil! Gone too are the days where out intellect was clouded by the notion that marijuana is some kind of harmful death drug.    </p>
<p>We have actually come as far as being able to safely say that between marijuana and alcohol, our Mary is probably the safer bet!</p>
<h1><b>Why is Marijuana Safer? </b></h1>
<p>The debate of which is safer is now so widely had that even the Business Insider did an online piece on the same! There are a number of particulars that make marijuana safer than alcohol without a doubt and we’re going to delve into some of them.</p>
<h2><b>Long Term Health </b></h2>
<p>The first thing that makes marijuana a safer bet is that when it comes to long term health risks, apart from respiratory problems for those who smoke, there are none others. Alcohol on the other hand has been linked to liver damage and failure, the growth of cancers and even dementia in the long term among other illnesses.</p>
<p>Comparing the two, we can safely say that long term heavy cannabis use is still healthier than equally heavy long term consumption of alcohol!</p>
<h2><b>Social Damage</b></h2>
<p>For those who drink; we’ve all had those mornings when we have woken thinking; “man I wish I hadn’t done/said that. On the other hand, after a few joints, chances are you may not want to do or say much in any case! At any rate not something you’d regret.</p>
<p>What we’re saying here is unlike alcohol, marijuana is not the kind of substance that will make you seek out trouble, get in people way or make a public fool of yourself in a big way! With alcohol, you can really go out there and make a mess of things in a matter of minutes. Guess who wins here? Mary Jane again!</p>
<h2><b>Motor Skills</b></h2>
<h2><b> </b></h2>
<p>Unless you suffer from some kind of condition or smoke too much in your first time, chances are, you’re never going to be so stoned that someone else has to carry you home! Alcohol can debilitate you to the point that you can’t stand on your own two feet.</p>
<p>Alcohol dampens and impairs motor skills and capacity in a way that marijuana doesn’t. Unlike marijuana, alcohol systematically shuts down your nervous system until a point that you are completely incapacitated.</p>
<p>When it comes to driving, though both may pose trouble, alcohol is hands down the bigger culprit. If you look at DUI cases, the bulk of them will involve people who have had one drink too many. Further, many of these will likely be classed as fatal. You won’t find any fatal DUI cases attributed to people strictly and exclusively under the influence of marijuana however! Again, marijuana here is safer.</p>
<h2><b>Violent and Reckless Behavior</b></h2>
<p>Numerous cases of domestic violence, child abuse, rape and even murder are linked to assailants being under the influence of alcohol and sometimes other hard drugs and substances. Alcohol has the tendency as many say; to bring out the very worst in people.</p>
<p>Individuals under the influence of alcohol who have had one drink too many are a risk to not just themselves, but to those around them; their loved ones included! For all the homes that alcohol has wrecked, you’d rarely hear of someone getting stoned and attacking their wife, kids or neighbors. You won’t hear of people getting stoned and partaking in unsafe sexual behaviors or cheating on their partners.</p>
<p>As numerous articles, blogs and even memes rightly state; “When you’re smoking weed, the only thing that is really at risk is your refrigerator!”</p>
<h2><b>Overdose and Withdrawal </b></h2>
<p>Last but not least, you cannot overdose on Marijuana. Especially not if what you are smoking is simply dry herb! Alcohol on the other hand at high levels can cause your entire central nervous system to shut down. This includes your heart and breathing. Marijuana does NO such thing.</p>
<p>Further, if you do develop a weed habit, though quitting is hard and sometimes unpleasant, that is about all it is. You cannot die from withdrawal nor does your body begin to implode. An alcoholic trying to clean up will among other things go through delirium tremors (DTs). Further, sudden cessation of drinking can even kill the person in question. We don’t think we need to highlight who wins this one!</p>
<h1><b>Winding Down</b></h1>
<p>We could go on with this blog, present evidence and keep cutting things down but we think the odds are pretty clear. Though moderation is the key to everything, if you want to know which the safer of the two is, it’s right there for you— Marijuana!</p>
<p>If you’re convinced, skip on the bar, swing by our online smoke shop, pick up a bong, pipe or bubbler and unwind without being a risk to yourself or anyone else!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/reasons-why-more-seniors-have-taken-up-cannabis-smoking-lately</id>
    <published>2019-02-20T12:49:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-02-20T12:50:15-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/reasons-why-more-seniors-have-taken-up-cannabis-smoking-lately"/>
    <title>Reasons Why More Seniors Have Taken Up Cannabis Smoking Lately</title>
    <author>
      <name>James Park</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Following the wide spread legalization of cannabis primarily for medicinal use as well as recreational use in some areas, numerous seniors have taken up smoking. According to a study conducted by the <i>U.S. National Institute of Health, </i>numerous Americans use cannabis for recreation as well as for healthcare purposes.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/reasons-why-more-seniors-have-taken-up-cannabis-smoking-lately">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Following the wide spread legalization of cannabis primarily for medicinal use as well as recreational use in some areas, numerous seniors have taken up smoking. According to a study conducted by the <i>U.S. National Institute of Health, </i>numerous Americans use cannabis for recreation as well as for healthcare purposes.</p>
<p>The question is; why have so many seniors suddenly taken up the habit?</p>
<div class="faux-h1"><b>Why More Seniors Have Taken Up the Habit</b></div>
<p>Given that seniors are smoking cannabis today, we researched some of the reasons why this may be so. Here is what we came up with.</p>
<h2><b>Legalities </b></h2>
<p>In the past, marijuana was inaccessible legally in most parts of the world. Mainstream medicinal use was unheard of. Legalization has not just made the herb accessible to people. It has also helped in un-demonizing cannabis making more individuals open to trying it out. Further, it is much easier to get hold of than it ever was before.</p>
<p>Legal cannabis also gives people a sense of safety and approval hence the willingness to give it a go.</p>
<h2><b>Pain and other Ailments</b></h2>
<p>Cannabis has become a viable replacement for a number of pain medications. This in particular with regards to opioid based medication which is known for its unpleasant and sometimes dangerous side effects as well as its potential for addiction.</p>
<p>Marijuana or cannabis is a much safer alternative when it comes to pain medication and is extremely effective due to CBD and THC present in it. Further it can be taken without the fear of unpleasant side effects, overdoes or reaction with other drugs and medication.</p>
<p>Marijuana or cannabis is also prescribed to supplement other treatments. Cancer and arthritis patients are often prescribed cannabis as a form of supplemental symptom relief.</p>
<h2><b>A Pleasant Alternative</b></h2>
<p>Cannabis as many of us know has some very pleasant effects. These include relaxation of the mind and body, an increased appetite and mild elation among others. Many seniors including those who were initially prescribed marijuana as medication, having enjoyed these affects have taken to recreational use.</p>
<p>Among these there are those who have tried the herb in their younger days and are okay getting back to it. There are others who thoroughly enjoy the affects as it helps reduce boredom and keeps things interesting. This is particularly so for seniors in retirement.</p>
<p>Finally there are those who have taken up smoking as a healthier alternative to the previously more socially acceptable substance use – drinking. The fact that cannabis has far less unpleasant side effects in comparison to alcohol and can be taken along with medication are among two of the reasons why this is so.</p>
<div class="faux-h1"><b>The Bottom Line </b></div>
<p>Keeping all this in mind, it makes perfect sense that many seniors would drop their use of substances like opioid based pain medication and alcohol in favor of this benign herb. If you’re someone who counts as a senior and have just taken up smoking – join the club!</p>
<p>For those looking to buy quality glass bongs, bubblers, pipes and other smoking accessories, there is no shortage of accessories and paraphernalia to choose rom!  You can even buy your bong<a href="https://www.bongoutlet.com/bongs"> </a>online by visiting a headshop like ours! In any case, happy blazing!</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/what-to-consider-when-finding-the-right-bong-for-me</id>
    <published>2019-02-20T12:42:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-02-20T12:43:54-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/what-to-consider-when-finding-the-right-bong-for-me"/>
    <title>What to Consider when Finding the Right Bong for Me?</title>
    <author>
      <name>James Park</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Choosing a bong for the first time or even replacing an old one in this day and age can require a fair amount of thought. This is because following the decriminalization as well as legalization of cannabis in certain places, manufacturing of smoking supplies has become a lot more mainstream. The result; a lot more to choose from!</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/what-to-consider-when-finding-the-right-bong-for-me">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Choosing a bong for the first time or even replacing an old one in this day and age can require a fair amount of thought. This is because following the decriminalization as well as legalization of cannabis in certain places, manufacturing of smoking supplies has become a lot more mainstream. The result; a lot more to choose from!</p>
<p>The question is where does one begin? How do you go about finding and selecting the perfect bong for yourself?</p>
<div class="faux-h1"><b>What to Consider When Finding the Right Bong </b></div>
<p>When you’re trying to find yourself the right bong, you need to take a few things into consideration. Here they are.</p>
<h2><b>What are you Smoking? </b></h2>
<p>This first question refers to what form you’re smoking your cannabis in. Are you someone who smokes dry herb, do you usually go for concentrate or is it an alternation between the two?</p>
<p>Though it doesn’t make too much difference and though you can smoke both in any kind of bong, it sometimes helps to keep a separate bong for concentrate from the one you use for your dry herb. This is in order to maintain flavor. We will elaborate on this further in the blog.</p>
<h2><b>Shape and Size</b></h2>
<p>Bongs are available in a number of shapes and sizes. These range from those you can simply hold to those you need to rest on the ground when taking a hit. You also have choice by way of shape from the extremely simple varieties to more complex designs.</p>
<p>When trying to figure out the right shape and size for your bong, one of the things you need to do is take into account your smoking habits. If you’re the sort who smokes with a lot of people and usually stick with pipes or joints when alone, a larger design might be more appropriate.</p>
<p>On the flipside, if it’s just you and maybe a housemate for the most part, a smaller design would do too.</p>
<h2><b>Down-stems and Percolators</b></h2>
<p>There was a time when most if not all bongs came fitted with down-stems. Today, however, you are offered a choice between those that come with and those that come without. Further, many bong designs today come with what you call percolators. These are used to filter as well as diffuse the smoke you are inhaling. Again, there are bongs available with multiple percolators and those with only one or two.</p>
<p>We mentioned in the first pointer that keeping two separate bongs was advisable. This comes into play here. Multiple percolators are preferable when you’re smoking dry herb. If you’re smoking concentrate however, you want to reduce the number of percolators as that amount of filtration won’t be needed!    </p>
<h2><b>Cost, Quality and Material </b></h2>
<p>Last but not the least, you need to check your budget as bongs today can range from affordable to pretty pricey depending on what you’re going for. You have different glass thicknesses as well as a range of qualities to choose from.</p>
<p>If you’re the sort to take good care of what you own and are into collecting things, you might want to go for one of the higher quality or novelty bong designs. If however you just want a bong for day to day use, you have numerous reasonably priced or cheap, good quality bongs for sale you can make your selection from.</p>
<p>The only thing that is important is that you’re clear on what you’re looking for.</p>
<div class="faux-h1"><b>The Upshot </b></div>
<p>When you’re looking to purchase a bong, keep the points above in mind and you’ll probably make the right choice! If you’re located in Canada or the U.S. and are looking for cool glass bongs for sale as well as other designs and models, check out our online headshop and take your pick! </p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/alleviating-arthritic-pain-with-cannabis</id>
    <published>2019-02-20T12:35:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-02-20T12:45:45-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/alleviating-arthritic-pain-with-cannabis"/>
    <title>Alleviating Arthritic Pain with Cannabis</title>
    <author>
      <name>James Park</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p><span style="text-decoration: underline;">Arthritis is an umbrella term</span> used to describe a variety of medical conditions that cause painful inflammation and stiffness in joints. It’s by far one of the most common medical conditions that plague the adult population of the world as recent estimates suggest that 54 million adults suffer from the condition.</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/alleviating-arthritic-pain-with-cannabis">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Arthritis is an umbrella term<span> </span>used to describe a variety of medical conditions that cause painful inflammation and stiffness in the joints. It’s by far one of the most common medical conditions that plague the adult population of the world. Recent estimates suggest that 54 million adults suffer from this condition.</p>
<p>With big pharmaceutical companies trying and failing to create a reliable cure for this condition, many people have turned to cannabis to address their symptoms. After all, the drug has been around for millennia, and countless civilizations have relied on it for its pain alleviating properties.</p>
<p>Today, we’ll be taking a closer look into why it makes sense to use cannabis to treat insufferable pain.</p>
<h2><strong>What Does The Medical Research Say?</strong></h2>
<p>Unlike other websites that bore the reader with thousands of case studies of people ‘claiming’ to benefit from using cannabidiol (CBD), we’ve decided to present the facts instead. So, for this section of our blog post, we’ll only be looking at medical papers published in respected medical journals.</p>
<p>A recent report (found in the European Journal of pain) explicitly states how marijuana consumption can lessen the effects of arthritis. In this case study, the research team applied CBD on mice who suffered from arthritic pain.</p>
<p>The medical team claims that tangible results could be seen from day one and it took only four days for the effects to become permanent! This medical paper goes on to claim that the drug reduced the degree o inflammation in the rats. This, in turn, lead to an unprecedented alleviation of pain!</p>
<h2><strong>Cannabis vs. Prescription Drugs – Which Is Better?</strong></h2>
<p>Right about now, you might be wondering,</p>
<p><em>What’s the big deal about cannabis? Why can’t I use a normal prescription drug (like Ibuprofen) instead? What’s the difference?</em></p>
<p>Given the fact that over the counter prescription drugs have become increasingly popular in recent years, it’s understandable if you have these concerns. However, what the big pharmaceuticals won’t tell you is the negative aspects of using pain killers.</p>
<p>It’s a little known fact that most over the counter pills are extremely addictive. There have been countless instances of athletes and rock stars who found it really hard to break their pain killer addiction, long after they had overcome their injuries.</p>
<p>The situation is so dire that many people have even died due to overdosing on prescription pills. The Centers for Disease Control (CDC) claims that more than 25,700 people died from overdosing on prescribed drugs!</p>
<p>On the other hand, we have cannabis which isn’t addictive to begin with. This makes it the ideal option for people who suffer from arthritic pain as the drug is just as effective (if not more) when it comes to alleviating pain. Furthermore, a grand total of zero people have died from a marijuana overdose which just goes to show the drug is completely safe for consumption.</p>
<h2><strong>In A Nutshell:</strong></h2>
<p>There’s overwhelming evidence that highlights the medical benefits of marijuana. The drug has remarkable anti-inflammatory properties that make the pain associated with arthritis more manageable.</p>
<p>It’s because of these reasons (and countless others) that doctors in multiple countries have switched to medical marijuana to treat people who suffer from arthritis and other pain causing conditions.</p>
<h2><strong>About OneWholesale.ca:</strong></h2>
<p>If you’re in the market for high-quality smoking accessories, then the<span> OneWholesale.ca</span><span> </span>team would love to help! We have an ever-expanding selection of top-notch bongs, bubblers, vaporizers and pipes<span> </span>to choose from that will make your next smoking session more fun and more memorable! Visit our website today to benefit from our remarkable<span> daily deals</span>.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/bong-101-choosing-the-right-bong</id>
    <published>2019-02-20T11:49:00-05:00</published>
    <updated>2019-02-20T12:27:34-05:00</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/bong-101-choosing-the-right-bong"/>
    <title>Bong 101: Choosing the Right Bong</title>
    <author>
      <name>James Park</name>
    </author>
    <summary type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>What are your criteria for finding a new bong? What should you consider before your next purchase? Find out how to choose the right bong for you!</p><p><a class="read-more" href="https://www.onewholesale.ca/blogs/news/bong-101-choosing-the-right-bong">More</a></p>]]>
    </summary>
    <content type="html">
      <![CDATA[<p>Whether you’re buying a bong for the first time or replacing your current piece, choosing one can often seem confusing. With so many different options out there, it is difficult to know where to start. Fortunately, this simple guide will help you figure out what you’re looking for. Here are the most important factors to consider when purchasing a bong:</p>
<h2><strong>Smoking needs</strong></h2>
<p>First and foremost, where and how often will you be using the bong? This is an important question to ask yourself. For example, if you’re planning to use the bong daily, you should purchase something that is easy to clean, such as a glass bong. However, glass bongs must be handled with caution, especially if large groups of people are sharing it. Consider these factors when you are making your decision.</p>
<h2><strong>Material</strong></h2>
<p>Bongs are made from different materials. But, glass, acrylic and ceramic are the most popular choices. Each material has its pros and cons:</p>
<p><strong>Glass: </strong>Stylish,strong and easy to clean,glass bongs are ideal for beginners and experienced smokers.The only downside is that glass cannot withstand extreme temperatures. Contrary to what many people believe, the latest bongs are made from sturdy glass, which makes them ideal for everyday use.</p>
<p><strong>Acrylic: </strong>Plastic or acrylic bongs are much more affordable than glass and ceramic. Available in various colors, plastic offers plenty of color choices to choose from. Plastic is also a translucent material. This means you can see the quality of the water in your plastic bong.</p>
<p><strong>Ceramic: </strong>Ceramic bongs are heavier than glass bongs. Unlike glass, ceramic bongs can tolerate extreme temperatures. However, the main problem with a ceramic bong is that it is harder to clean than glass.</p>
<h2><strong>Size </strong></h2>
<p>Next up, you need to ensure you’re getting the right sized bong. Size can make or break your smoking experience. Smaller bongs are easier to use and carry around. If you’re travelling, smaller bongs will be easier to pack than larger ones. If you prefer bigger bongs, keep them in a safe location to minimize the risk of damage and breakage. Also, bigger bongs are easier to pass around among larger groups.</p>
<h2><strong>Accessories</strong></h2>
<p>Last but not least, bongs come with different accessories, such as a difuser, to elevate your smoking experience. Accessories also improve the aesthetic appeal of a bong. Whether you’re looking for high quality bongs or smoking accessories, OneWholesale.ca is a one-stop source for all your smoking needs. Visit our website to place an order.</p>]]>
    </content>
  </entry>
</feed>
